<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-27T15:15:25-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Literally Lauren</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Davy — I mean, Daisy</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/story/2018/12/09/davy-daisy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Davy — I mean, Daisy" /><published>2018-12-09T15:44:57-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-09T15:44:57-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/story/2018/12/09/davy-daisy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/story/2018/12/09/davy-daisy.html">&lt;p&gt;Hi, Daisy! How was school today?” Daisy’s mom had been asking that same question every day since school started back last month. Usually, Daisy answered, “Okay,” or even, “Great!” Sometimes she threw in a “Fantabulous!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But today she said, “Awful. I’m super mad at Davy. He kept bothering me.” She paused and waited for her mom to say, “No!” Or even “That IS awful!” Or throw in an, “I’m going to call Mrs. Grayson the minute we get home!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But all her mom said was, “Oh?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yes! Mrs. Grayson moved our seats and now he’s next to me and he keeps trying to get me to talk when we are supposed to be working and he’s always getting out of his seat AND he kicks the chair legs!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It sounds like he has a lot of energy,” her mom admitted. “Maybe he has a tough time dealing with it sometimes. That must be hard. Poor Davy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only Daisy thought she said, “Poor Daisy.” She nodded. “Poor me. It is hard. He’s so distracting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh. Well, yes, I am sorry that you’re getting distracted. But I actually said, ‘Poor Davy,’” her mom explained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Poor Davy!?” Daisy repeated with wide eyes. “Why Davy?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well, think of how it must feel to have a hard time sitting still.” She smiled at Daisy in the mirror. “Maybe if you knew what he goes through every day, some of that anger might go away.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy didn’t want to argue, but she wasn’t so sure her mom was right about this.  Daisy never had to be reminded to sit in her seat or to get back to her work. It wasn’t hard at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy was still mad at Davy the rest of the afternoon and evening right up until bedtime. As her mom tucked her in, Daisy said, “Can you please ask Mrs. Grayson to move my seat back? I don’t want to sit next to Distracting Davy anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see…” her mom answered in the voice that actually meant, “Nope.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But for now, remember what I said and try to imagine what it would be like to have all that energy. It might change how you feel. Night!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took Daisy awhile to fall asleep because she had so many upset thoughts to listen to. “Tomorrow means more school and more sitting next to Davy and more chair kicking. And more talking. And more getting out of his seat. Why can’t he just do what he’s supposed to? Like me.” She remembered what her mom said, but when she tried to imagine having extra energy, she thought, “I could still do it. I could just sit and listen and finish my work. It wouldn’t be that hard being like Davy….” and with that last thought, she fell asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, Daisy walked into her classroom and saw Davy already sitting in his seat. “Oh, right.” She sighed to herself. “I guess I better get ready for a morning of Distracting Davy. He probably hasn’t even started his morning work yet.” She peeked at his paper and saw that Davy was already almost finished with the entire page. Huh. That was…different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another different thing seemed to be Daisy’s chair. It was a little harder than usual. It was really hard, actually. Elgh. And why did the insides of her legs feel so itchy? Daisy reminded herself she had a whole page to get started on and decided to ignore the hard chair and the itchy legs. She stared at her paper in front of her and tried to focus. But ignoring them didn’t work. The chair only seemed to get harder and her legs only seemed to feel itchier and twitchier. She tried swinging them a tiny bit. That felt better. Plus, when her heels hit the bottom of her chair legs, it made a fun little bump. Bump, bump, bump. Daisy wrinkled her nose with delight. Just by kicking her chair legs, she made her whole body jump all the way up to her hair. Oh, fun, and she could even make the desk and her pencil jump. Bump! Bump! Bump!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Davy looked over at her with an annoyed look. “What?” Daisy whispered. He didn’t say anything but looked down at her swinging legs. Daisy decided to take a break. Davy had that look of someone about to raise their hand with a tattle. Her legs immediately went back to feeling like they wanted to dance or run off of their own. And her chair felt harder than ever. She slowly tried to stand up on one leg with her knee still on the seat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Daisy, have a seat!” Called out Mrs. Grayson. Daisy felt her cheeks get hot. She sat down with a thump and was determined to sit there for the rest of the morning. Even if the chair felt like sitting on a rock. Or a cliff. A rocky, lumpy cliff. Maybe it wasn’t even the same chair! Maybe someone switched it because it was the hardest worst chair ever and now they had Daisy’s nice, regular chair. Daisy stood up to check. Oh. Okay, so it was the same chair. There was that little black mark from when she had dropped a marker last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Daisy, stay in your seat for a few more minutes until that work is done and then we’ll move to the carpet for a story,” her teacher reminded her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy’s throat felt tight as she sat back down. She hadn’t even realized she had been standing again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The carpet also felt strange and non-cozy this morning. Daisy couldn’t help wiggling a bit. Which was why she got two Looks from Mrs. Grayson. And another Look when she asked someone near her a question. Not to mention a “Daisy, stop tapping your foot and listen to the story, please.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was turning out to be a rough morning and it was taking so much longer than normal. When it was time to go back to her desk for math fact practice, Daisy dreaded that chair. “This is silly,” she told herself. “Just going to sit and follow directions. Like I always do. It will be easy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She sat down and picked up her pencil and made it through a few addition problems when she dropped her pencil. As she picked it up, she noticed Davy’s shoes. Ooh, he was wearing yellow shoe laces. No…they were lime green. No…yellow? It didn’t matter. Definitely yellow. Probably. She better check. “Davy…” she whispered. He didn’t move. “Davy.” She said it a little louder. Still nothing. “Davyyyyyyy- Davy! What color are your laces? Yellow?” He definitely heard her this time. She could tell because he sighed and turned away from her as he finished the last problem. She frowned. That didn’t seem necessary. But also, maybe…familiar? Didn’t she do that to him yesterday? “Hey“ she was about to ask him why he was acting mad when Mrs. Grayson spoke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Davy- I mean Daisy-let’s hold off on talking until lunch. You need to hurry and finish that page. Davy, you’re doing an awesome job and working hard this morning!” Daisy felt her mouth open in surprise. What. Her teacher just called her Davy. And gave him a compliment about working hard! Distracting Davy!? But, come to think of it…Daisy realized that Mrs Grayson hadn’t reminded Davy to sit still or stay in his seat or stop talking. Not even once! But she had to remind Daisy…because Daisy was distracted today…and now Davy was getting mad… Wait a minute…Daisy tapped her pencil as she thought. She needed to talk to her friends as soon as possible. She just had to make it- Daisy checked the clock- 8 more minutes until lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Daisy, focus on your work!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As soon as Daisy and her friends got to their lunch table, she blurted out, “I switched places with Davy!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But, you’re in the same seats as yesterday.” June said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No, I’m acting like him.” Daisy explained.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kate gasped. “You switched bodies? That’s so cool! I didn’t know that could happen in real life!” Kate leaned in closer. “Davy?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy sighed. “No, it’s still me, I’m just acting like him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, I get it,” said Roxi. “Like the time the Stewart twins switched places and we couldn’t figure out why Carly was talking louder and didn’t know where to sit but then we found out it really Alice?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But Daisy and Davy don’t look like each other at all!” said June.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, yeah,” admitted Kate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Their names sound alike,” chimed in Roxi. “Does that matter?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They all turned to look at Daisy. She shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t really know, but he’s acting like me and I’m acting like him. I keep getting in trouble for moving and talking but he’s getting all his work done and just sitting there! And he’s getting mad at me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, that is backwards. Right? “Roxi said. “Weren’t you mad at him yesterday for talking to you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yes!” Said Daisy. “I was mad at him all day and even when I was trying to fall asleep!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh oh,”said Kate. “When you were falling asleep? Are you sure it was while you were falling asleep?” Kate said the words “sure” and “falling asleep” very slowly and clearly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah…it that bad?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do you remember- this is important- do you remember the very last thing you thought about?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Um, I think I tried to imagine what it would be like to be like Davy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And did you start feeling different as soon as you woke up?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I guess so,” Daisy said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kate nodded like she had been expecting that answer. “Well, you made a wish or something. That’s what happens in movies and books. The last thing you think about, sometimes it becomes a wish and comes true in the morning.” She calmly went back to eating her lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Really?!” Daisy, on the other hand, was not feeling calm at all. “What do I do?!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, it’s totally fine, don’t worry. You do have to spend the whole day with your wish coming true, though. Just make sure that when you are about to fall asleep that you wish to be yourself again- and then in the morning, that wish comes true and everything is back to normal!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;June, Roxi, and Daisy looked at each other. It did make sense. But tonight seemed like a very, very long time from now. With a very uncomfortable chair. And very active legs. Daisy let her head fall onto the table with a thump. “I have to spend the rest of the day getting in trouble and being Davy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It won’t be that bad,” June tried to make her feel better. “Just try harder not to talk or be wiggly.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah!” chimed in Roxi. “It’s not that hard!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were wrong. It was hard. Daisy knew a lot of the answers to her work but kept finding herself whispering to someone next to her. And her body just didn’t want to SIT anymore. She kept kicking her chair without meaning to and Davy was definitely giving her mad and grumpy looks. “Which doesn’t help at all,” She thought to herself. She began daydreaming about getting outside. Recess couldn’t come soon enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it was finally recess time, Daisy ran with June, Kate, and Roxi to the part of the field where the tallest clover flowers grew. Daisy only lasted a few minutes of tying the stems around each other when she jumped up. “Does anyone want to play tag?!” She asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The others looked up. “But..we said yesterday that we were going to make the school record clover chain…” June said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know, I really wanted to help but..can we just run around real quick first?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wait!” Kate said. “What’s Davy doing?” They looked around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There he is!” Daisy pointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What is he doing? Is he…” Kate squinted. “He’s building a fort out of the mulch. That’s something you would do, Daisy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah!” Roxi agreed. “He always runs around and plays tag or soccer or something!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Come on, guys.” Said Kate, standing up and shaking the broken bits of leaves and stems off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This will have to wait until tomorrow. Let’s help Davy-oops, I mean, Daisy-get her energy out.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later, Daisy had to admit, she had never had so much fun running as fast and as long as she could. As they headed back inside, she was relieved that her legs lost some of their itchiness. Only one hour of school left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How was school today?” Her mom asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was okay.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy looked out the window.  “But I’m sorry that I was so mad at Davy yesterday. I think you’re right- it’s hard having that much energy sometimes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh. Well. Okay!?” Her mom seemed surprised.  “That’s very… reflective of you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy wasn’t sure what reflective meant but her mom made it sound like it was a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night as she got into bed, she kept repeating to herself, “I hope I’m myself tomorrow. I want to be myself tomorrow.” She paused. And just before thinking turned into sleeping, “I want to be myself, but without the getting mad at Davy part.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back at school the next morning, Daisy’s chair felt like her regular chair again and she was able to focus on her work until it was done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Davy was back to wanting to stand up and whisper. But she smiled at him and whispered, “Talk later, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She waited until recess and just as Mrs. Grayson told everyone they could go play, she ran over to Davy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hey, sorry, I didn’t want to talk while we were supposed to be working. But… did you have a weird day yesterday?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Davy thought. “Yeah, it was kinda weird. I didn’t feel like playing soccer. But I’m definitely going to today.” He started to run towards the field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hey!” Daisy called. Davy turned around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daisy didn’t know how to start. At last she said, “Um, you’re good at running. You’re really fast…and…sorry if I’ve been mean and getting mad at you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Davy grinned. “Yeah, sorry I talk to you in class a lot. I just forget. But not yesterday.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah,” Daisy agreed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Davy took off after the rest of the kids playing soccer, Daisy thought, “I forget, too. But not yesterday.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hi, Daisy! How was school today?” Daisy’s mom had been asking that same question every day since school started back last month. Usually, Daisy answered, “Okay,” or even, “Great!” Sometimes she threw in a “Fantabulous!”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hammie and Robin</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/story/2018/12/07/hammie-and-robin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hammie and Robin" /><published>2018-12-07T15:44:57-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-07T15:44:57-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/story/2018/12/07/hammie-and-robin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/story/2018/12/07/hammie-and-robin.html">&lt;p&gt;Hammie loved running on his hamster wheel more than anything. He loved the feeling of his heart beating stronger and faster. He loved running so fast that the wheel became a blur above him and below him and all around him. He loved the way the wheel created a little breeze for his fur. He was certain that nothing could ever be more fun than running.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day started off like any other day. Hammie was running on his wheel when he noticed tiny chubby fingers reaching for the bars of his cage. “Awww! The baby learned to stand! And now he can reach all the way up here! Isn’t that cute?” Hammie thought to himself. “He’s growing up so fas-“ and then Hammie wasn’t thinking about anything because he was too busy squeaking as he began to fall. Hammie fell and his wheel fell and his cage fell and they all landed on the floor with a crash. Hammie blinked. He didn’t feel hurt, so that was good. The baby seemed okay, that was very good. Then he saw that his wheel was broken. “That’s not so good.” Thought Hammie sadly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie was so sad that he didn’t pay too much attention to what was happening for the next few minutes. He crawled into his little hamster house and stayed there. He heard footsteps as his little girl ran into the room and then everything was being picked up and he heard things like, “Poor Hammie!” “needs a new one!” “maybe tomorrow” and “move him to a safer place ”. The door to his cage opened and his broken wheel was taken out. The cage was set back down and soon everything was quiet. 
Hammie peeked out and instead of the usual view of the playroom, he was staring out a big, clear window. Hammie looked around him and realized his cage had been moved up to the top of the bookshelf. “ Oh,wow! I can see clouds! And trees! And kids and houses and there’s so much to look at! I’m going to be so busy! Look at that furry squirrel, he looks fun. Oh, look at the car driving! Look at that mailbox! Ooh, look at that robin flying! She looks friendly!”
And from his new place on the bookshelf near the window, Hammie watched and looked and saw and only missed his wheel a tiny bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie was right about the robin. She was friendly. As she flew by the window, she saw him and thought, “Oh, what a sweet looking hamster! I never saw him before. I’ll go say hello!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when she flew closer, she saw that the window was closed. Since she couldn’t talk to him, she waved. “He’s waving back!” She smiled. “I knew he was nice. I can meet soon. For now, I suppose I’ll go back to flying!” and off she went.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin loved to fly. She loved having the cool ground under her feet one minute and then deciding to fly up into the warm sunlight a moment later. She loved seeing how fast she could swoop in a circle, how close she could get to the ground, and that no branch was too high for her to land on. She never felt stuck or bored because she could always fly away. She believed nothing could ever be more fun than flying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, Hammie woke up to the sound of a plastic bag opening. He stuck his face out of his house and saw his cage door opening and….a brand new wheel being placed right in the middle of his cage! He couldn’t believe it! A wonderful new view and a new wheel! “Oh, I’m so happy the baby learned to stand!”he thought with glee. He hopped right in and ran and ran until his little world once more became a happy, joyful blur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin was also having a wonderful morning and she flew and flitted from place to place. When she flew by the hamster’s window, she noticed it was still closed. She flew back once more to look inside to see what he was doing. He running so fast on a wheel that she couldn’t even see his feet. She flew by a third time to try to wave at him again but he was so busy running he didn’t see her. “Oh, well, maybe next time” she thought to herself as she flew off into the warm morning sunshine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it went for the next few days. Robin flew, Hammie ran, and the window stayed closed.
Robin felt sorry for the little hamster who lived in a cage and couldn’t fly. “All that work and he never gets to go anywhere. It’s like he’s stuck. I hope he isn’t sad,” she thought to herself. 
Meanwhile, Hammie had been watching the robin. She didn’t seem to stay in one place very long. She was always flying off. Hammie noticed her feet hardly ever touched the ground. “Maybe it’s hard for her to run.” Hammie felt sorry for the bird who was always having to fly off and never got to run. “I hope she isn’t sad,” he thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then one day, a very special thing happened. Well, it started off as an accident in the kitchen. The kids in Hammie’s family forgot about some cookies baking in the oven. The whole house smelled like burnt chocolate and butter. The family opened all the windows to get the smell out. Robin happened to fly by just as the playroom window was pushed up.
“The window! It’s open! At last!” She tweeted to herself and flew down to say hi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie was having a particularly fast run that day. The wheel was squeaking especially loudly. It was so loud that he didn’t hear the friendly “Hi!…hello? Hello?” Until he happened to look over and see a bird standing on the windowsill. He was so surprised that he tripped and went flying right off the wheel.
“Oh, no! Are you okay?!?” The bird asked. 
Hammie giggled. “Oh, yes, I’m fine, thanks! I didn’t see you there. I was having such a fun run on my wheel. My name is Hammie.” He climbed onto the bars of the cage to get closer to the windowsill.
“I’m Robin” the bird chirped. “So…it was a fun run?” She asked. She sounded surprised.
Hammie was surprised that she was surprised. “Oh, yes, it’s always fun.” Then he remembered that he never saw her running. “I mean, um..well… flying looks fun, too?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin thought the little hamster sounded sad. “Yes, it is. And guess what I just decided? You’re going to go flying today!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie giggled again. “Oh, I can’t fly.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin hopped on her little birdie feet with excitement. “Of course you can! You can hold onto my back and I’ll take you for a ride!” Hammie had not been expecting this. He accidentally let go of the bars and dropped to the floor of his cage.“I don’t think that will work!”  He squeaked. 
Robin was determined. “If you can hold onto bars, you can hold onto feathers.”
That was a fair point. But Hammie remembered something just in time. “Oh, but my door is closed! I guess I can’t.” He smiled and raised his shoulders in a shrug but before his shoulders were back down, Robin had hopped on the shelf and popped the lock open with her beak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie was still smiling, but not because he was happy. Because he forgot how to move anything, even his face. “Oh. You know how to open doors. And mine is now…open. That’s…so surprising.	”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Climb on, my new friend who is named Hammie! You’ll love it!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie swallowed. “Well. Okay…I guess a quick flight would be….fine…” he slowly climbed out of his cage and onto Robin’s back. Before he could say, “Maybe we should start off slowly” Robin had already taken flight, was out the window and above the roof of the house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie squeaked with a terror he had never felt before, not even when the baby pulled his cage down. He couldn’t see the ground and couldn’t tell where the sky was or how high they were. It felt like he was falling in all different directions and without ever landing. All he could do was squeak as loudly as he could with his tiny hamster voice and hope Robin could hear him so she would stop flying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin did hear Hammie but she thought he was squeaking with joy. “It’s the same squeak he makes on his wheel, but louder! He must be having even more fun than when he’s running on his wheel!” She thought happily. It was an easy mistake to make- she didn’t realize that earlier she had heard the wheel squeaking, not Hammie. Hammie didn’t squeak when he was having fun. Only when he was scared stiff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally and at last, Robin circled back to the window and landed gracefully next to his cage. Hammie dropped off immediately and ran dizzily back inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Was it so much fun? Was it the best fun you’ve ever had? I’m so glad it worked!” Robin twittered. “I’ll tell you what, I will check every day and whenever the window is open, I’ll come back and give you another ride, okay?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No that’s okay I’m fine i mean thank you so much for offering but really I probably shouldn’t fly anymore I mean the window is never open usually and besides I can’t ask you to do that and anyway that was sort of the most terrifying thing I’ve ever done and I may not be able to sleep tonight but thank you that’s very kind.” Hammie said at all once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin blinked. “Oh. I thought you were having so much fun. I mean, flying is the best feeling there is! It’s complete freedom, maybe if you tried it again-“&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“NO!” Squeaked Hammie. “Honestly, I do appreciate you being so kind, but that wasn’t very fun for me. At all. I’m much happier running on my wheel.  Because, actually, running is the best feeling. Now that I have tried flying, I know what it’s like. There’s too much space and directions and my stomach feels like it’s missing. It’s definitely not as fun as running.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin shook her head. “No, running isn’t as much fun as flying. It’s a little dangerous actually. Big, hunting animals might be able to catch you when you run, but not if you fly.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Of course!” Hammie hadn’t thought of this. “You’ve never run on a wheel before! It’s delightful! You get to run and run without ever worrying about where you’re going and you never get lost and it’s perfectly safe!” He smiled and clapped his paws together. “Go for a run on my wheel! You’ll love it!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin smiled patiently. “Well, I can’t fit into your cage or the wheel so it wouldn’t-“ but before she could finish, Hammie had already pushed the wheel until it was directly under the open cage door. 
“Here’s what you do- you can run on the top of the wheel! The door is big enough that you can get your legs inside.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin was still smiling but not because she was happy. She was too confused to remember how to move anything, even her face. “Well, I suppose that could work but-“&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie jumped up and down with excitement. “Yay! Hop on!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ok, I guess a quick run would be….fine…” Robin didn’t want to hurt her new friend’s feelings, so she gently hopped onto the cage and through the open door. She put her feet on the top of the wheel. Before she could say, “I’ll just start with a slow walk,” Hammie gave the wheel a giant push. 
“Go, Robin! You’re doing great! Look at you! You’re having so much fun, you can’t even talk!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Robin wasn’t having fun. Robin couldn’t talk because she realized that if she stopped running, even for a second, she would crash into the roof of the cage and get stuck. Hammie had given her such a mighty push (very surprising for such a tiny animal) that she had to run as fast as her legs could go to stay on the wheel. Just when she thought it was starting to slow enough that she could hop off, Hammie said, “Don’t worry, the fun isn’t over yet!” And gave it another enormous push. Robin’s bird legs had never been so tired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, at last, Hammie decided to hop into the wheel and slow it down. He couldn’t wait any longer to ask Robin how much she had loved running on his wheel. Robin hopped onto the window sill and tried to catch her breath.  Hammie began chattering. “Isn’t that the most fun? Your feet were going so fast! Probably as fast as flying, maybe even faster! And you weren’t in danger at all, so that was the first time you could just run without worrying and you just felt joyful, right?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Not exactly.” Robin managed to tweet. “I was about to fall the whole time! I couldn’t keep up!”
“Oh, really? I’m so sorry!” Hammie said. He thought for a moment. “Well, next time, we’ll start off slower-“&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin interrupted him. “No that’s okay there doesn’t need to be a next time honestly that exhausting and difficult and it was pretty awful and I can’t breath and how do you enjoy that I can’t feel my feet they hurt so badly!” She said all at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie blinked. Robin blinked. “Oh.” They both said at the same time. “Well.” They both said at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The thing is” Robin tried. “I know we’re new friends and all, and I don’t want to be rude, but I think you’re wrong. It just seems impossible that someone couldn’t love flying.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know what you mean, except to me it seems wrong to say that you don’t enjoy running.” Hammie said. He tapped his little hamster paw fingers together.
  “Maybe the word we’re trying to to think of isn’t ‘wrong…’ It’s different.” Robin said slowly.
“Of course! You’re right! That’s it!” Hammie said happily.
“What’s it?” Robin was confused.
“Different!”
“Right, it’s different.” Robin tried to explain again. “It’s not wrong, but I don’t know what it is.”
“It’s different!” Hammie said.
“What is?” Robin asked.
Hammie took a deep, cheerful, and patient breath. “We’re not wrong that we don’t like the same things! We’re just different! It’s not wrong that you like to fly. It’s not wrong that I like to run!”
“Oh!” Said Robin. “We’re just different from each other! I get it! Why didn’t I think of that?”
“You did! You just didn’t know you did!” Hammie giggled.
They heard someone starting to climb up the stairs. 
“I think they’re going to close the window,” said Hammie. “I hope you can visit me again the next time the window is open.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I will!” Promised Robin. “I’ll fly by and check every day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And I’ll be right here, running.” Hammie smiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin smiled too as she flew out the window. She looked back as she saw Hammie get back on his wheel to run. He did seem happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hammie looked out the window at Robin as she flew off through the trees. He was glad she was flying. He knew she loved it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hammie loved running on his hamster wheel more than anything. He loved the feeling of his heart beating stronger and faster. He loved running so fast that the wheel became a blur above him and below him and all around him. He loved the way the wheel created a little breeze for his fur. He was certain that nothing could ever be more fun than running.</summary></entry></feed>